80stees.com 2019-12-17

# 80sTees.com Privacy Policy

Updated May 22nd, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.80sTees.com (the "site").

Your Information

We use the information you provide to us in connection with your use of our site (e.g., name, shipping/billing address, phone number, email address and credit card information) for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order, spotting trends, and informing you about 80sTees and our partners. We may maintain a record of your product purchases, and we may also share and/or cross-reference information about you, including, without limitation, contact information and data, with partners to enable them to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. We may contract with, and share and/or cross-reference such information and data with, third parties to provide certain services including, but not limited to, credit card processing, shipping, data management, security and information verification, and promotional services. We may disclose information when required by law, to enforce our site policies, or to protect our rights, property or safety, and/or the rights, property, or safety of any third party. We may also share information with agencies or companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation, but we will not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

Please note that we do not alter our site's data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

Your Credit Card Number

We do not store your credit card information, nor do we have access to your credit card number. All credit card data is processed by a PCI-compliant third party payment processor.

Your Email Address

80sTees will not sell your email address. We will not contact you with promotional email unless you opt-in to our email list. We use your email address to send you transactional email messages. Transactional email messages include: Order Confirmation, Shipment Notification, Delivery Notification, Request for Product Reviews, and any other email communication needed to facilitate your order.

We use a number of services to send both transactional and marketing emails.  These services store your email address for the purpose of maintaining your status as a subscriber, for the purpose of recording whether you have received and/or opened emails from us, and to ensure that all emails that were supposed to be sent to you were actually sent.

You will be given the option to add your email address to our mailing list when you place your order. We suggest you do, because we give out discount coupons and announce sales from our mailing list. You can unsubscribe from our marketing email list here.

Your Phone Number

We only call our customers if it is necessary to ask a question about an order. We do not sell or rent your phone number. We do not like getting sales calls, and we will not subject our customers to it.

Your Physical Address and Contact Information

Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information and promotions from 80sTees.com. Periodically we may partner with other companies that want to send promotional material via the postal service to our customers.

Your Device Information

While you are using our site we may record your preferences and browsing history to our database. This information is used so that we may better serve you via our website and/or third party websites. This data may be used to recognize you when you visit our site and to promote products similar to products you have ordered in the past. Your preferences are collected and you are recognized via cookies that are placed on your web browser. 80sTees places cookies on your browser through Google Analytics as well as some third party advertising companies. 

We sometimes partner with companies who can place banner ads to 80sTees.com on other websites. If you have been to our site in the past you may see 80sTees.com banners more frequently since we target people who have visited the site in the past. In addition, the ads you see may be based upon your browsing history while on 80sTees.com. So if you visited a page about Sesame Street t-shirts you may see ads for Sesame Street t-shirts from 80sTees.com while you are visiting other websites. We partner with a variety of advertising companies to display these ads, including google.com and Facebook. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve the badge on the site and to serve ads based on your prior visits to the site. 

Opting Out

You can opt out from Google Serving ads based on your actions on 80sTees.com and other sites by going to the [Google Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?sig=ACi0TCiRDcnrXrdffABE6Nifr9QppTwHkj_NTB8gd0FaMd9YV_wg5YIp3OvYIp-y-pdTWNhIhLjQXh6TyIek2jcL233J8XokduMKuR1N-zHOJP2Ls6zIAM_wKkwTu-xTmML-Aucg-KSrCOB6oLAL11n-sPX9rEefGBMsmC7iVBTJsDKZmWkr3jnzCeVGR-wzwiV8cGO96yfR&hl=en). You can also install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) as well.  

You can control your Facebook Ad settings by visiting their [Ad Preferences](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads) page.

If you would like to opt out of our exchange of your information with other marketers, please let us know by sending us an email at help@80stees.com, including your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically what information you do not want to receive, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to implement your request as promptly as possible. You may opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/).

Hotjar

On occasion, we use [Hotjar](http://www.hotjar.com/) in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy by clicking on this link.

You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this [opt-out link](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

California Shine the Light Law

Under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain, once per calendar year, information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information from us, please use the Contact Us link on the site, write "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line of your message,and we will send you a reply email containing the requested information. Not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

Consent to Processing of Information in the United States

Notwithstanding your country of origin, or country, state and/or province of residence, by utilizing our site and/or directly providing personal information to us, you hereby agree to and acknowledge your understanding of the terms of this privacy policy, and consent to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and/or in other jurisdictions as determined by us.

Children

We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). The site is not directed at children under the age of thirteen (13), and by using the site, you represent that you are not under the age of thirteen (13).

Right to Transfer

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary set forth in this Privacy Policy, 80sTees reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer your personal information to a third party in connection with a proposed or actual purchase, sale, merger, or any other type of acquisition or financing of all or any portion of 80sTees.

Changes 

If we change our privacy policy, we will inform you by posting the revised policy on our site, noting the date of revision. Your continued use of our site after such change constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised privacy policy.
